curriculum vitae(C.V)

Mohd Nasir Hussain

DOT NET DEVELOPER(SOFTWARE DEVELOPER)

- 91 8652484812
- Nhussainit90@gmail.com
- Room number201, neha sana Building naya nagar Mira Road East, Mumbai – 401 107.
- 17th Dec 1990
- www.linkedin.com/in/nasirhussain

ABOUT ME

A dynamic IT professional with 4.5 years of experience in .Net Development, presently working as Software development.

Looking to obtain the position of Software Developer in a fast-paced tech environment to utilize well-honed skills in computer science and extensive experience in developing customized software based on varying client demands.

CAREER OBJECTIVE:

Problem solver and strong communicator eager to prove my value and talent at an emerging company like Revature. Motivated to advance and expand my skill set through targeted mentorship and challenging project.

SKILLS

7/10

Angular.JS, JavaScript, jQuery, Ajax, Json

8/10

SQL, ORACLE, Mongo DB, LINQ

7/10

Postman

8/10

ASP .net, C#, MVC.net, Web API

8 / 10

HTML, CSS, BOOTSTRAP, .Net Framework

EDUCATION

MCA

Salem University (Mumbai swami Vivekananda college)

2013 - 2015

B. Com

Salem University (Mumbai swami Vivekananda college)

2009 - 2012

HSC

Goenka school Rajasthan board 2006 – 2007

HOBBIES:

News reading, Cricket

NATIONALITY:

INDIAN

MARITAL STATUS:

UNMARRIED

PASSPORT NUMBER:

J2590535

EXPERIENCE

Dot Net Developer

Writer Information Management / Mumbai – Andheri(Marol) / July 2019 – Present

Jagjivan Ram Hospital:

- We enable the patient to register on the site using His personal information and patient document search and add new pdf file
- Oracle is used as a Database.
- Handle entire application with all modules
- Role Based User Creation
- MIS Report, Audit Log Creation
- Patient Document Upload with Template and Search Document with Name and Template.
- Multiple websites management from one platform, User-friendly Interface.
- Improved and designed monitoring systems to address issues with system stability and quality of data.
- Bulk Upload File Application in Windows Application

Renault India Pvt Ltd.:

- Website was developed for an invoice Processing.
- Create Qr code Csv data upload
- Different type of Reports creates with entire show data in Reports
- Bulk Upload File Application in Windows Application

Tata Starbucks:

- Website was developed for an HR and Finance Data Processing.
- Created Dynamic webpages using MVC5 Entity framework
- Creating HR Finance Data uploading page and search with HR and Finance data page wise creating LOG report edit HR and Finance data page
- Creating MIS report for showing data
- Tagging wise data document show.

Narayana Health Care:

Create RDLC Report entire project with sql database and mvc.net.

<u>Ambit:</u>

 PDF BulkUploding data with CSV Data and PDF Uploading Data more than 5 gb data.

Error log when data not uploading

Second Experience:

Software Developer

JK IT Solutions LLP / Mumbai – 400 069 / November 2017 – April 2019

Mace Cure Hospital:

It offers many services Web Applications, Web sites, Offline software.

- Web forms create, Reports Generate.
- Managing the website and resolving the issue if any occurs
- Only work on changing the design of the previous project which is provided by the team.

Making Asp.net C#, SQL stored procedures, interacting with testers and resolving bugs. Strong relational database knowledge.